Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
And I was like, "Bitch, if you don't send me black car
وقلت، "يا عاهرة، إذا لم ترسلي لي سيارة سوداء"
I'm walking.
أنا أمشي.
Oh, my God, so true.
يا إلهي، هذا صحيح تمامًا.
He got one for Isabelle.
حصل على واحدة لإيزابيل
Oh, my God, I know, right?
يا إلهي، أنا أعلم، أليس كذلك؟
And did you see how he was looking at her?
وهل رأيت كيف كان ينظر إليها؟
Oh, I saw. Gross.
أوه، لقد رأيت. مقرف.
Gigi, go.
جيجي اذهبي
Go.
يذهب.
Did you notice how everyone started dancing
هل لاحظت كيف بدأ الجميع بالرقص؟
after we hit the floor?
بعد أن وصلنا إلى الأرض؟
Oh, yeah.
أوه نعم
I felt like I was hosting the entire club.
لقد شعرت وكأنني أستضيف النادي بأكمله.
I mean, what, I said hi to like, three people,
أعني، ماذا، قلت مرحباً لثلاثة أشخاص،
and then all of a sudden it was like,
ثم فجأة أصبح الأمر مثل،
“Oh my God, come hang out with us,”
"يا إلهي، تعال واقضِ بعض الوقت معنا"
or like, “Can we join you?”
أو مثل، "هل يمكننا الانضمام إليك؟"
It was like, dead before we showed up.
لقد كان الأمر كما لو أننا ماتنا قبل ظهورنا.
Gigi, walk.
جيجي، امشي.
Bitch, go.
يا عاهرة، اذهبي.
It's exhausting being this hot.
إنه أمر مرهق أن يكون الجو حارًا إلى هذا الحد.
I know.
أنا أعلم
Oh my God, I'm so done with this dog.
يا إلهي، لقد انتهيت من هذا الكلب.
Oh my God, I love your dog.
يا إلهي، أنا أحب كلبك.
I swear it's not even intentional.
أقسم أنه ليس مقصودًا حتى.
People just like, follow my vibe.
الناس يحبون فقط أن يتبعوا أسلوبي.
Is that a thing?
هل هذا شيء؟
Like natural rhythm or something?
مثل الإيقاع الطبيعي أو شيء من هذا القبيل؟
I don't think
لا أعتقد
it was just your vibe.
لقد كان مجرد شعورك
Oh, shut up, skank. I'm just magnetic.
أوه، اسكتي يا عاهرة. أنا مجرد مغناطيسية.
Um, Kat.
اممم، قطة
Tommy just showed up outside my door.
لقد ظهر تومي للتو خارج بابي.
Whoa, he's looking fine.
واو، إنه يبدو بخير.
Wait, seriously?
انتظر، بجدية؟
Mm-hm, yeah.
ممم، نعم.
- I gotta go. - Good luck.
- يجب أن أذهب. - حظا سعيدا.
Oh, and hey, don't get chlamydia.
أوه، ومهلاً، لا تصاب بالكلاميديا.
I've heard rumors.
لقد سمعت شائعات.
Ew, what the fuck.
إيه، ماذا بحق الجحيم؟
Bitch.
عاهرة.
Ew.
هذا.
Gigi, go potty now.
جيجي، اذهب إلى الحمام الآن.
Come on, bitch.
تعال يا عزيزتي.
Mommy is tired and coming down hard.
أمي متعبة وتنزل بقوة.
Let's go binge something.
دعنا نذهب لتناول شيء ما.
Ugh. Seriously?
اوه، بجدية؟
Never rains in LA.
لا تمطر أبدًا في لوس أنجلوس.
What the hell?
بحق الجحيم؟
Baby. Chill.
يا حبيبتي، استرخي.
Gigi?
سن؟
Baby. Mommy's coming.
حبيبتي، أمي قادمة.
Oh, my God. Gigi!
يا إلهي. أسنان!
Oh, my God.
يا إلهي.
You fucking bitch! Bitch!
يا لك من عاهرة! يا لك من عاهرة!
You killed my Gigi. You killed--
لقد قتلت جيجي. لقد قتلت--
Fucking coyotes.
الذئاب اللعينة.
Did anybody hear about the
هل سمع أحد عن
social media influencer
مؤثر على وسائل التواصل الاجتماعي
that became roadkill last night?
هذا ما حدث عندما دهست سيارة على الطريق الليلة الماضية؟
Another coyote attack this morning,
هجوم ذئب آخر هذا الصباح
this one in Sherman Oaks.
هذا في شيرمان أوكس.
Why do you think this keeps happening?
لماذا تعتقد أن هذا يحدث باستمرار؟
Well, for one, coyotes aren't picky eaters.
حسنًا، أولًا، الذئاب ليست من الحيوانات التي يصعب إرضاؤها في الطعام.
They're opportunistic predators.
إنهم مفترسون انتهازيون
They're not above nipping at you
إنهم ليسوا فوق العض عليك
to send a message if they feel threatened.
لإرسال رسالة إذا شعروا بالتهديد.
Wildfires are pushing coyotes deeper
حرائق الغابات تدفع الذئاب إلى عمق أكبر
into Los Angeles neighborhoods.
إلى أحياء لوس أنجلوس
They're desperate.
إنهم يائسون
They're going to do what they have to do
سيفعلون ما يجب عليهم فعله
to survive.
للبقاء على قيد الحياة
A boy was pulled off his bike on a residential street.
تم سحب صبي من على دراجته في شارع سكني.
Did that actually happen?
هل حدث ذلك فعلا؟
Goddamn Hollywood elites.
لعنة الله على النخبة في هوليوود.
We've got rats in the walls?
هل لدينا الفئران في الجدران؟
Oh, yeah.
أوه نعم.
Yeah. Rats will spawn six to 12 a litter,
نعم. تفرخ الفئران من ستة إلى اثني عشر في كل بطن.
with up to six litters a year.
مع ما يصل إلى ستة مواليد في السنة.
That's 60 rats, right there, all from one big mama rat.
هذا 60 جرذًا، هناك، كلهم ​​من أم جرذ كبيرة واحدة.
But--but how? It's a new house.
لكن... لكن كيف؟ إنه منزل جديد.
Well, look around. Yeah.
حسنًا، انظر حولك. نعم.
Contractors use cheap drywall, plastic instead of copper,
يستخدم المقاولون ألواح الجبس الرخيصة والبلاستيك بدلاً من النحاس،
and rats...
والجرذان...
rats will chew through just about anything.
الفئران سوف تقضم أي شيء تقريبًا.
Yeah, you got doggy doors, water and gas lines.
نعم، لديك أبواب للكلاب، وخطوط المياه والغاز.
Nice family.
عائلة لطيفة.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Yeah, drains, toilet vents.
نعم، المصارف، وفتحات المراحيض.
Trust me when I say you do not want
صدقني عندما أقول لك أنك لا تريد
one of those nasty little critters
أحد تلك المخلوقات الصغيرة المزعجة
climbing out of your toilet.
الخروج من المرحاض الخاص بك.
Ugh, yeah.
أوه، نعم.
I don't even want to think about that.
لا أريد حتى أن أفكر في هذا.
Then don't.
إذن لا تفعل ذلك.
Look. Rats are vermin. - Right.
انظر. الفئران حشرات ضارة. - صحيح.
They're a disease.
إنهم مرض.
They want your shelter, your food, your water,
إنهم يريدون مأواك وطعامك وماءك.
your happiness, your sanity.
سعادتك، عقلك.
And they wiggle their little bodies
وهم يهزون أجسادهم الصغيرة
through any nook or cranny they can find
من خلال أي زاوية أو ركن يمكنهم العثور عليه
until they get it.
حتى يحصلوا عليه.
Okay.
تمام.
So what do we--what do we do?
إذن ماذا نفعل؟ ماذا نفعل؟
Do you really have to poison them?
هل يجب عليك حقا تسميمهم؟
Can't you just, like, trap them and, like,
ألا يمكنك فقط اصطيادهم و، مثل،
relocate them to the desert or something?
نقلهم إلى الصحراء أو شيء من هذا القبيل؟
Oh, yeah. Make them nice little suitcases and bath towels?
أوه، نعم. اصنع لهم حقائب صغيرة لطيفة ومناشف حمام؟
No. You don't send them to a day spa.
لا، لا ترسلهم إلى منتجع صحي نهاري.
You gotta wipe them out.
يجب عليك القضاء عليهم.
Send a message to all the other rats in the area.
أرسل رسالة إلى جميع الفئران الأخرى في المنطقة.
This house right here is off limits.
هذا المنزل هنا محظور الدخول إليه.
Right.
يمين.
Just thinking like, are rats even that bad?
مجرد التفكير، هل الفئران سيئة إلى هذه الدرجة؟
You ever hear of a little thing called the Black Plague?
هل سبق لك أن سمعت عن شيء صغير يسمى الطاعون الأسود؟
Millions and millions of people dying horribly,
ملايين وملايين من الناس يموتون بشكل فظيع،
bleeding out of their eyes, their ears, their a--
النزيف من عيونهم، آذانهم، أفواههم
I got it. Rats bad.
لقد فهمت. الفئران سيئة.
Poison good.
السم جيد.
Oh, this is not good, Scott.
أوه، هذا ليس جيدا، سكوت.
Oh.
أوه.
But now that... that's your biggest problem.
ولكن الآن... تلك هي مشكلتك الأكبر.
That's like a rat paradise.
إنها مثل جنة الفئران.
That's my neighbor's yard.
هذه ساحة جاري.
I'll go ahead and spray it anyway.
سأذهب وأرشها على أية حال.
You're welcome.
على الرحب والسعة.
No, no. It's my-- I don't own that part.
لا، لا. هذا الجزء خاصتي، لا أملكه.
Is he a customer?
هل هو عميل؟
He's soon to be.
إنه سيكون كذلك قريبا.
Hey, Chloe.
مرحبا، كلوي.
Little help, please?
مساعدة بسيطة من فضلك؟
Wasn't going with you enough?
ألم يكن الذهاب معك كافيا؟
No, it wasn't. And that's rude.
لا، لم يكن كذلك. وهذا وقح.
Come on, come help.
تعال، تعال للمساعدة.
Come on.
تعال.
What's with the attitude, huh?
ما الأمر مع هذا الموقف، أليس كذلك؟
It's like this happened overnight.
يبدو الأمر وكأن هذا حدث بين عشية وضحاها.
So then she ghosted me, moved to Turkey or something.
وبعد ذلك تجاهلتني، وانتقلت إلى تركيا أو شيء من هذا القبيل.
Oh, man. Oh, that sucks.
يا رجل. أوه، هذا يمتص.
Sorry. Just to go back to what we were saying earlier
عذرًا، فقط للعودة إلى ما قلناه سابقًا.
about the pricing plan. So you said there's like--
بخصوص خطة التسعير. إذًا قلتَ إن هناك...
My dad fell down the stairs, had a stroke.
سقط والدي من على الدرج وأصيب بسكتة دماغية.
We're back. Finally.
لقد عدنا، أخيراً.
Hey, kid.
مهلا يا صغيري.
Charlie's psyched to see you.
تشارلي سعيد لرؤيتك.
We got rats in the walls.
لقد حصلنا على الفئران في الجدران.
Oh, I told you there's rats.
أوه، لقد قلت لك أن هناك جرذان.
I saw one squirming under the garage door the other night.
رأيت واحدًا يتلوى تحت باب المرآب في الليلة الأخرى.
It was gross. - Yeah, I'm already on it.
لقد كان الأمر مقززًا. - نعم، أنا على هذا بالفعل.
He's also gonna set Trip's house on fire for us.
إنه سوف يشعل النار في منزل تريب من أجلنا أيضًا
Oh, good. It's an eyesore.
أوه، جيد. إنه منظر قبيح.
Do us a favor.
افعل لنا معروفا.
Afraid I can't help you there.
أخشى أنني لا أستطيع مساعدتك هناك.
Oh, I was just kidding.
أوه، كنت أمزح فقط.
Well, that's my time.
حسنًا، هذا هو وقتي.
Alrighty.
حسنا.
Well, I'm gonna set some traps, do some spraying,
حسنًا، سأقوم بوضع بعض الفخاخ، وأقوم ببعض الرش،
and I'll be back in a few days to check everything out.
وسأعود خلال بضعة أيام للتحقق من كل شيء.
Okay. Thanks a lot, Devon.
حسنًا. شكرًا جزيلًا، ديفون.
- Oh, one more thing. - Yeah.
- أوه، شيء آخر. - نعم.
Oh. Rats love dog food.
أوه. الفئران تحب طعام الكلاب.
So you might want to get rid of the, uh, the dog.
لذا ربما تريد التخلص من الكلب.
The dog food?
طعام الكلاب؟
The dog.
الكلب.
No. No, that's okay.
لا ، لا، لا بأس بذلك.
You let me know. No extra charge.
أخبرني بذلك. لا توجد رسوم إضافية.
No, but no.
لا، ولكن لا.
That's not even-- so no on that.
هذا ليس حتى-- لذلك لا على ذلك.
Did he say he was gonna get rid of the dog?
هل قال أنه سوف يتخلص من الكلب؟
Think he was kidding.
أعتقد أنه كان يمزح.
That's weird.
هذا غريب.
And creepy.
و مخيفة.
He's just passionate about what he does.
إنه متحمس لما يفعله.
He came highly recommended.
لقد جاء موصى به للغاية.
Oh shit.
يا للقرف.
Okay, I'll be in my office.
حسنًا، سأكون في مكتبي.
Good to see you.
يسعدني رؤيتك.
It was a rare encounter,
لقد كان لقاء نادرا
but there was a Scott sighting.
ولكن كان هناك رؤية سكوت.
He's almost done with his deadline, honey.
لقد انتهى تقريبًا من الموعد النهائي، عزيزتي.
We'll have more time with him soon.
سيكون لدينا مزيد من الوقت معه قريبا.
Sure we will.
بالتأكيد سنفعل.
We will. I promise.
سنفعل ذلك. أعدك.
Where's the candy?
أين الحلوى؟
The National Weather Service
الخدمة الوطنية للأرصاد الجوية
has issued another red flag warning
أصدر تحذيرًا آخر بالعلم الأحمر
with gusts expected to reach up to 60 miles per hour
مع هبات متوقعة تصل سرعتها إلى 60 ميلاً في الساعة
in Hollywood this evening.
في هوليوود هذا المساء
Hey.
مرحبا.
What's up?
ما أخبارك؟
Um... are you at all worried about the tree out front?
اممم... هل أنت قلق على الإطلاق بشأن الشجرة الموجودة أمام المنزل؟
Because they just said that the storm
لأنهم قالوا للتو أن العاصفة
was going to be really crazy tonight,
سيكون الأمر مجنونًا حقًا الليلة،
and you did say that you were going to trim it last year.
وقلت أنك سوف تقوم بقصه العام الماضي.
No, it's fine.
لا، إنه بخير.
It's going to be fine.
سيكون كل شيء على ما يرام.
Okay.
تمام.
I'm not worried.
أنا لست قلقا.
Yeah.
نعم.
They always try to make shit sound worse
إنهم يحاولون دائمًا جعل الأمور تبدو أسوأ
than it is on the news.
مما هو موجود في الأخبار.
Remember the killer bees?
هل تتذكر النحل القاتل؟
Remember how long we heard about them?
هل تتذكر كم من الوقت سمعنا عنهم؟
-  Mm-hm. - When I was a kid,
- ممم-هم - عندما كنت طفلاً،
I was afraid of all bees.
كنت خائفة من جميع النحل.
Ever seen one killer bee?
هل سبق لك أن رأيت النحل القاتل؟
Did anyone ever die from a bee?
هل مات أحد من النحلة؟
I mean, that wasn't allergic.
أعني، هذا لم يكن حساسية.
No. I'm not worried. -  Okay.
لا، أنا لست قلقًا. - حسنًا.
It's fine. It's gonna be fine.
لا بأس، سيكون بخير.
If you say so.
إذا قلت ذلك.
- I know so. -  All right.
- أعلم ذلك. - حسنًا.
Okay.
تمام.
Can we not do movie night?
هل يمكننا أن لا نقوم بليلة الفيلم؟
It's cringe.
إنه أمر محرج.
I thought you loved movie night.
اعتقدت أنك تحب ليلة الفيلم.
Not anymore.
ليس بعد الآن.
-  Scott, pizza's here. - Got it.
- سكوت، البيتزا هنا - فهمت.
You're young.
أنت شاب.
And you're not the pizza.
وأنت لست البيتزا.
No, I'm not a pizza.
لا، أنا لست بيتزا.
Unless you want me to be one?
إلا إذا كنت تريدني أن أكون واحدا منهم؟
Uh... Wait, is this...1202?
أوه... انتظر، هل هذا...1202؟
Nope. This is 1208.
لا، هذا ١٢٠٨.
That's 1202.
هذا هو 1202.
Shit!
اللعنة!
Shoot. I mean, uh... sorry.
أطلق النار. أعني، آه... آسف.
So sorry.
أنا آسف جدًا.
Fuck me! It's windy out here.
يا إلهي! الجو عاصف هنا.
Oh, my God, why?
يا إلهي لماذا؟
Where's the--where's the pizza?
أين البيتزا؟ أين البيتزا؟
That wasn't it. That was--
لم يكن هذا هو الأمر. كان ذلك--
It was one of Trip's whores.
لقد كانت واحدة من عاهرات تريب.
We don't call them that, Chloe.
نحن لا نسميهم بذلك، كلوي.
Yeah, not good.
نعم ليس جيدا.
It was one of Trip's friends that he pays for.
لقد كان أحد أصدقاء تريب هو الذي يدفع له المال.
- Yeah. - Oh, well--
- نعم. - أوه، حسنا--
So then what would you call it?
إذن ماذا تسميه؟
A prostitute?
عاهرة؟
A ho? A tramp-- - No! No, no.
إلى هو؟ إلى المتشرد-- - لا! لا، لا.
No, Chloe.
لا، كلوي.
Scott, a little help. - Of course. No.
سكوت، بعض المساعدة. - بالطبع. لا.
Chloe, those are not good words to use for a woman, for anyone,
كلوي، هذه ليست كلمات جيدة لاستخدامها مع امرأة، أو أي شخص،
whether or not she may or may not have, you know, sex.
سواء كان بإمكانها ممارسة الجنس أم لا، كما تعلم.
No, you just still want to be respectful,
لا، أنت فقط تريد أن تكون محترمًا،
so you would use a term like, um... lady of the night.
لذا يمكنك استخدام مصطلح مثل، أمم... سيدة الليل.
Chloe, that's a good one.
كلوي، هذا جيد.
Like a vampire.
مثل مصاص الدماء.
Yeah, except she doesn't suck blood.
نعم، باستثناء أنها لا تمتص الدماء.
She's--
إنها--
Let's table this conversation until after dinner.
دعونا نؤجل هذه المحادثة إلى ما بعد العشاء.
Good, good. Yeah. It's--
جيد، جيد. نعم. إنه--
Or until you turn 18. Whenever.
أو حتى تبلغ سن 18 عامًا . متى شئت.
But--
لكن--
Please be the pizza.
من فضلك كن البيتزا.
Charlie?
تشارلي؟
Okay.
تمام.
What is it, boy?
ما الأمر يا فتى؟
Hey, you're okay.
أهلا، أنت بخير.
Hey, what's--what's out there?
مهلا، ما الذي يوجد هناك؟
What page you on?
في أي صفحة أنت؟
Hold your horses, mister. I'm almost done.
تمهل يا سيدي، لقد انتهيت تقريبًا.
Okay, missus.
حسنًا سيدتي.
Well...?
حسنًا...؟
I am going to need a couple of days
سأحتاج إلى بضعة أيام
to really form an opinion.
لتكوين رأي حقيقي.
Are you serious?
هل انت جاد؟
No. It's really good.
لا، إنه جيد حقًا.
- Really? - Yeah, it's really good.
- حقا؟ - نعم، إنه جيد حقًا.
Really? - Mm-hm.
حقا؟ - مم-هم.
Like, don't let this go to your head,
مثل، لا تدع هذا الأمر يؤثر على رأسك،
but it might actually be a masterpiece.
ولكنها قد تكون في الواقع تحفة فنية.
- Are you serious? -  Mm-hm.
- هل أنت جاد؟ - مم-هم.
What's your favorite part?
ما هو الجزء المفضل لديك؟
I'll tell you tomorrow.
سأخبرك غدا.
Okay. It can-- it can wait till tomorrow.
حسنًا، يُمكنه الانتظار حتى الغد.
Okay.
تمام.
Guys, guys, guys!
يا شباب، يا شباب، يا شباب!
- Oh. - There's something outside.
- أوه. - هناك شيء في الخارج.
Uh huh.
اه هاه.
I--I just heard an animal, and it's hurt,
لقد سمعت للتو حيوانًا، وهو متألم،
and we need to go right now and go and help.
ونحن بحاجة إلى الذهاب الآن والذهاب للمساعدة.
Oh, um...
أوه، أم...
Uh...
أوه...
Well...
حسنًا...
Come on.
تعال.
Okay, okay. Let's... let's check it out.
حسنًا، حسنًا. لنلقِ نظرة.
Okay. Give me--give me--
حسنًا. أعطني-أعطني-
-  No, right now. - No? Right now. Okay.
- لا، حالًا. - لا؟ حالًا. حسنًا.
Whoa.
واو.
Whoo.
وو.
Let's see.
دعونا نرى.
Whoo-hoo. Wow.
وو هوو. واو.
Oh, it was a--it was a tree.
أوه، لقد كانت شجرة.
It's just a tree.
إنها مجرد شجرة.
No. There was a dog.
لا، كان هناك كلب.
Make sure it's okay.
تأكد من أن الأمر على ما يرام.
Honey, I think it was just a tree.
عزيزتي، أعتقد أنها كانت مجرد شجرة.
Oh, hold on. Hold on.
أوه، انتظر. انتظر.
Shoo.
شو.
Hey, shoo. Shoo!
مهلا، شو. شو!
What was it?
ماذا كان ذلك؟
Just a sketchy little coyote. No big deal.
مجرد ذئب صغير مشبوه. لا بأس.
Now let's all go back to our own beds.
الآن دعونا نعود جميعا إلى أسرّتنا.
Charlie and his little one,
تشارلي وطفله الصغير
we can recreate exactly where we were before.
يمكننا إعادة إنشاء نفس المكان الذي كنا فيه من قبل.
Oh shit.
يا للقرف.
Oh! Oh, my God.
أوه! أوه، يا إلهي.
Oh no. Oh.
أوه لا. أوه.
Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck.
أوه، اللعنة. أوه، اللعنة. أوه، اللعنة.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
أوه، لا، لا، لا، لا، لا، لا، لا.
Oh no, no.
أوه لا، لا.
Oh, Jesus, fuck.
أوه، يسوع، اللعنة.
Fucking shit.
اللعنة عليك.
Ahh. It's not that bad.
اه. ليس سيئا إلى هذه الدرجة.
Oh, God.
يا إلهي.
It's not great.
إنه ليس رائعًا.
We wanted a new one.
أردنا واحدة جديدة.
Oh, shit.
يا للقرف.
Oh, my God.
يا إلهي.
It's gonna be okay, honey.
كل شيء سيكون على ما يرام، عزيزتي.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
Oh. Oh.
أوه. أوه.
Jesus.
عيسى.
I should have trimmed the tree.
كان ينبغي لي أن أقوم بتقليم الشجرة.
While the rest of LA felt the storm,
بينما شعر باقي سكان لوس أنجلوس بالعاصفة،
the hills bore the brunt of its fury,
تحملت التلال وطأة غضبه
suffering the worst of the damage,
يعاني من أسوأ الأضرار
with downed trees and widespread power outages.
مع سقوط الأشجار وانقطاع التيار الكهربائي على نطاق واسع.
What an idiot.
يا له من أحمق!
God.
إله.
Oh, yeah, that's just great.
أوه نعم، هذا رائع جدًا.
Oh, God.
يا إلهي.
Lucy.
لوسي.
Oh. Oh, it's so gross.
أوه. أوه، إنه أمر مقزز للغاية.
Make sure you get it all.
تأكد من حصولك على كل ذلك.
Do you want to do it?
هل تريد أن تفعل ذلك؟
Ew. As if, Dad. As if.
إيو. كأنه يا أبي. كأنه.
It's congealed, and it's like, ground into the concrete.
لقد تجمد، وأصبح مثل، مطحون في الخرسانة.
I'm gonna throw up.
انا سأتقيأ.
Hey.
يا.
You can just leave the food at the door.
يمكنك فقط ترك الطعام عند الباب.
You don't have to make a big thing of it.
لا يتوجب عليك أن تجعل من الأمر شيئًا كبيرًا.
Uh, what food?
أوه، أي طعام؟
I ordered Thai food.
طلبت طعامًا تايلانديًا.
I--I don't-- I'm the neighbor.
أنا-أنا لا- أنا الجار.
Like, yeah.
مثل، نعم.
Trip! Door!
رحلة! باب!
Wait, how do you guys have power?
انتظر، كيف لديكم القوة؟
Generator. Trip says he's gonna go off the grid soon.
مولد كهربائي. يقول تريب إنه سيُفصل عن الشبكة قريبًا.
Screw the man.
اذهب إلى الجحيم مع الرجل.
Oh. It's Liv.
أوه، إنها ليف.
Hey. - Hey, Trip.
مهلا. - مهلا، تريب.
I thought you were my-- I thought you were--
اعتقدت أنك كنت--
you were somebody else.
لقد كنت شخصًا آخر.
How you doing? - Good. How are you?
كيف حالك؟ - بخير. كيف حالك؟
-  Good. - You look good.
- جيد. - أنت تبدو جيدا.
I'm okay, yeah.
أنا بخير، نعم.
How's Stu? - Scott.
كيف حال ستو؟ - سكوت.
- Scott, sorry. - Yeah. He's good.
- سكوت، آسف. - نعم. إنه جيد.
He's pulling it together. Doing well.
إنه يجمع شتات نفسه، ويبلي بلاءً حسنًا.
Hey, listen. If you're...
مهلا، استمع. إذا كنت...
if you're looking for some water,
إذا كنت تبحث عن بعض الماء،
we can't help you.
نحن لا نستطيع مساعدتك.
I mean, we barely have enough.
أعني أننا بالكاد لدينا ما يكفي.
No.
لا.
No. Trip, do you have a cat?
لا، تريب، هل لديك قطة؟
Lucy. Is she okay?
لوسي، هل هي بخير؟
Um, well, we found this in our driveway.
حسنًا، لقد وجدنا هذا في ممر السيارات الخاص بنا.
-  That's her collar. -  So, yeah.
- هذا طوقها - إذن، نعم.
Just gonna give that to you. - Ew.
سأعطيك هذا فقط. - إيو.
You found this in your driveway?
هل وجدت هذا في الممر الخاص بك؟
Did you leave the door open again?
هل تركت الباب مفتوحا مرة أخرى؟
Okay, I'm gonna go.
حسنًا، سأذهب.
Did you leave the door open? Okay.
هل تركت الباب مفتوحا؟ حسنا.
I told you to watch the door. - Bye.
لقد قلت لك أن تراقب الباب. - وداعا.
- ...Thai food. I'm hungry. - Lucy!
- ...طعام تايلاندي. أنا جائع. - لوسي!
Here, kitty kitty, kitty kitty.
هنا، كيتي كيتي، كيتي كيتي.
Thankfully, no fires broke out last night,
لحسن الحظ، لم تندلع أي حرائق الليلة الماضية،
but road closures have swamped emergency services regardless.
ولكن إغلاق الطرق أدى إلى إرهاق خدمات الطوارئ على أي حال.
Expect delays for the next 24 hours.
توقع حدوث تأخيرات خلال الـ 24 ساعة القادمة.
Stay safe out there, LA.
ابقى آمنًا هناك، لوس أنجلوس
Maybe--maybe turn a bit
ربما--ربما تتحول قليلا
to the left, Scott. - What's that?
إلى اليسار، سكوت. - ما هذا؟
Maybe try and move at a different angle...
ربما حاول التحرك بزاوية مختلفة...
To the right? This way? Straight down?
إلى اليمين؟ من هنا؟ إلى الأسفل مباشرةً؟
Yeah.
نعم.
You sure that's on the right setting?
هل أنت متأكد من أن هذا هو الإعداد الصحيح؟
There's only one setting, I think.
هناك إعداد واحد فقط، على ما أعتقد.
It's just forward and reverse.
إنه فقط للأمام والخلف.
Really?
حقًا؟
I've been doing this for like 20 minutes,
لقد كنت أفعل هذا لمدة 20 دقيقة تقريبًا،
and it looks like an animal just kind of clawed at it.
ويبدو الأمر كما لو أن حيوانًا خدشها للتو.
Wow. Hey.
واو. مرحبا.
- Pretty cool, huh? - Yeah.
- رائع جدًا، أليس كذلك؟ - نعم.
I wanted to bring the chainsaw,
أردت أن أحضر المنشار،
but, of course, Sheila said, “No.”
ولكن بالطبع قالت شيلا "لا".
Well, that's probably for the best.
حسنًا، ربما يكون هذا هو الأفضل.
Oh, but good news. Tony said we got really lucky
أوه، لكن الخبر السار. قال توني إننا كنا محظوظين جدًا.
that the tree didn't damage the gas main.
أن الشجرة لم تتسبب في إتلاف أنبوب الغاز الرئيسي.
Could have been a lot worse.
كان من الممكن أن يكون الأمر أسوأ بكثير.
Trust me, you don't want a gas leak.
صدقني، أنت لا تريد تسرب الغاز.
One small spark and boom.
شرارة صغيرة و دوي.
Bye, bye, Dream House.
وداعا، وداعا، بيت الأحلام.
Huh. Well, that's great.
هاه. حسنًا، هذا رائع.
That's a silver lining.
هذه هي البطانة الفضية.
That's right. Oh shit.
هذا صحيح. أوه اللعنة.
Whether it's a seal
سواء كان ختمًا
straying too far from the shore--
الابتعاد كثيرًا عن الشاطئ
I'm seriously concerned your dad's gonna lop off an arm.
أنا قلق جديا من أن والدك سوف يقطع ذراعه.
...scattering in confusion.
...التشتت في الارتباك.
He's built stuff before.
لقد بنى أشياء من قبل.
Things that are pre-assembled.
الأشياء التي تم تجميعها مسبقًا.
Much like their terrestrial counterparts,
تمامًا مثل نظرائهم الأرضيين،
sharks are opportunists.
أسماك القرش انتهازية
They don't waste energy.
إنهم لا يهدرون الطاقة
Did you know most shark attacks
هل تعلم أن معظم هجمات القرش
are because they mistake us for seals?
هل هذا لأنهم يخطئون في اعتبارنا فقمات؟
Did you know most seal attacks happen
هل تعلم أن معظم هجمات الفقمة تحدث
because they mistake us for kelp?
لأنهم يخطئون في اعتبارنا عشب البحر؟
Mom, that wasn't funny.
أمي، هذا لم يكن مضحكا.
Put a bit of elbow grease into it.
ضع القليل من شحم الكوع فيه.
Maybe the battery could be a bit lower too.
ربما يمكن أن تكون البطارية أقل قليلاً أيضًا.
It could--it could be.
من الممكن أن يكون.
You sure that's on the top setting?
هل أنت متأكد من أن هذا في الإعداد العلوي؟
Can I just have your phone?
هل يمكنني الحصول على هاتفك؟
Oh. Oh, sorry, I only have 30%.
أوه، أوه، آسف، لدي 30٪ فقط.
So?
لذا؟
So no.
لذا لا.
God.
إله.
I can't believe she's gone.
لا أستطيع أن أصدق أنها ذهبت.
How do you know?
كيف علمت بذلك؟
You only looked for her for like five minutes.
لقد بحثت عنها لمدة خمس دقائق فقط.
You're right. I'm a fucking idiot.
أنت على حق. أنا أحمق تمامًا.
God damn it.
اللعنة عليك.
She's probably out there, she's scared to death.
ربما أنها موجودة هناك، وهي خائفة حتى الموت.
She's probably pissed at me. - Yeah.
ربما أنها غاضبة مني. - نعم.
I'm gonna go find her.
سأذهب للبحث عنها.
Oh yeah, great idea.
أوه نعم، فكرة عظيمة.
But maybe leave the gun.
ولكن ربما ترك البندقية.
You're right.
أنت على حق.
Uh-oh.
أوه أوه.
Oh. What the hell, Trip?
أوه، ماذا بحق الجحيم يا تريب؟
I think the generator went out.
أعتقد أن المولد خرج.
- How am I gonna charge my phone? - I don't know.
- كيف سأشحن هاتفي؟ - لا أعرف.
Have you thought about unplugging it?
هل فكرت في فصله؟
Might be good for your mental health.
ربما يكون مفيدًا لصحتك العقلية.
Jesus Christ.
يسوع المسيح.
Lucy!
لوسي!
You're a great host, Trip.
أنت مضيف رائع، تريب.
Thanks!
شكرًا!
What?
ماذا؟
Oh, shite.
أوه، اللعنة.
Missed a few texts from Sheila.
لقد فقدت بعض الرسائل النصية من شيلا.
Uh-oh.
أوه أوه.
Looks like she needs my expertise on the grill.
يبدو أنها بحاجة إلى خبرتي في الشواية.
Yeah, I get it.
نعم، فهمت ذلك.
When Liv summons me, I don't waste any time either.
عندما تستدعيني ليف، لا أضيع أي وقت أيضًا.
-“Summons me”? - Well.
-"استدعائي"؟ -حسنًا.
Nobody summons me, mate.
لا أحد يستدعيني يا صديقي.
I'm my own man.
أنا رجل خاص بي.
Remember that.
تذكر ذلك.
Yeah, no, I didn't.
نعم، لا، لم أفعل.
Okay, yeah, my bad.
حسنًا، نعم، خطئي.
Fuck. I gotta go.
يا إلهي، يجب أن أذهب.
Tell Sheila Liv and I say hi... or don't.
أخبر شيلا ليف وأنا أقول مرحباً... أو لا تفعل.
She's the worst.
إنها الأسوأ.
Hey, babe.
مرحبا يا حبيبتي.
-  Where are you, Tony? - Yeah.
- أين أنت يا توني؟ - نعم.
Yeah, just leavin' now. Just leavin' now.
نعم، سأغادر الآن. سأغادر الآن.
Yeah? Are you coming home?
نعم؟ هل ستعود إلى المنزل؟
Told you I got carried away.
أخبرتكِ أنني ابتعدت
You know what Scott's like.
أنت تعرف ما هو سكوت.
Man can't take a piss on his own.
لا يستطيع الإنسان أن يتبول بمفرده.
all this shit.
كل هذا الهراء
I'll be home soon. Okay? Yeah.
سأعود إلى المنزل قريبًا. حسنًا؟ نعم.
-  Screw you. - I love you.
- اذهب إلى الجحيم. - أحبك.
Dickhead.
أحمق
For fuck's sake.
من أجل اللعنة.
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
Shoo!
شوو!
Go on. Get the fuck out of here.
إذهب، إخرج من هنا.
What are you looking at?
ماذا تنظر اليه؟
What?
ماذا؟
What the hell's wrong with them?
ما الذي حدث لهم بحق الجحيم؟
Oh. Oh, it's the kid.
أوه، إنه الطفل.
Hey. Um, do you hear that sound?
مهلا، هل تسمع هذا الصوت؟
Help!
يساعد!
Sounds like somebody's singing or... dying.
يبدو الأمر وكأن شخصًا يغني أو... يموت.
Stay back. Get back.
ابقى في الخلف. ارجع.
No!
لا!
Does Stu sing?
هل ستو يغني؟
Wait a minute.
انتظر دقيقة.
No, it's gone now.
لا، لقد ذهب الآن.
Huh. Anyway.
هاه. على أية حال.
'Sup...
'رشفة...
Um, are you okay?
اممم هل انت بخير؟
Yeah, I'm okay. Why? Don't I look okay?
نعم، أنا بخير. لماذا؟ ألا أبدو بخير؟
No. You look like you have the flu.
لا، يبدو أنك مصاب بالأنفلونزا.
No, it's just these allergies.
لا، إنها مجرد هذه الحساسية.
It's... y'know.
إنه... كما تعلم.
Can I help you?
أيمكنني مساعدتك؟
Is your mommy or your daddy home?
هل والدتك أو والدك في المنزل؟
Mom!
أم!
That weirdo from next door is here.
هذا الشخص الغريب من البيت المجاور موجود هنا.
Look, I'm standing right here.
انظر، أنا واقف هنا.
I can hear that.
أستطيع سماع ذلك.
You think Lucy was in the tree when it fell?
هل تعتقد أن لوسي كانت في الشجرة عندما سقطت؟
Yeah.
نعم.
But you haven't seen any sign of her?
ولكنك لم ترى أي علامة لها؟
Well, just the collar.
حسنًا، فقط الطوق.
So the collar could have slipped off, right?
لذا فإن الطوق قد ينزلق، أليس كذلك؟
There's a possibility.
هناك احتمال.
So stop flirting with me, Liv, and help me find her.
لذا توقفي عن مغازلتي، ليف، وساعديني في العثور عليها.
Here, kitty, kitty, kitty, kitty.
هنا، قطة، قطة، قطة، قطة.
- Lucy! - Here, Lucy.
- لوسي! - هنا، لوسي.
- Come on. - Here, sweet princess.
- تعالي. - هنا، يا أميرتي الحلوة.
Here, girl. Here, girl.
هنا يا فتاة. هنا يا فتاة.
Here, sweet kitty.
هنا، القطة الحلوة.
Lucy. Good girl, kitty.
لوسي. فتاة جيدة، يا قطتي.
Mom, what are you doing?
أمي ماذا تفعلين؟
We're helping Trip find his cat.
نحن نساعد تريب في العثور على قطته.
- But it's dead. - Definitely missing.
- لكنها ماتت. - مفقودة بالتأكيد.
Uh-huh. Lucy.
اوه هاه. لوسي.
Come on. Good girl. - Oh, I think I see her.
هيا. فتاة جيدة. - أوه، أعتقد أنني أراها.
Oh, honey...
أوه عزيزتي...
Lucy... Lucy girl...
لوسي... لوسي الفتاة...
No. No, no, no.
لا. لا، لا، لا.
Oh, God. No.
يا إلهي. لا.
What am I gonna do now?
ماذا سأفعل الآن؟
No pictures!
لا يوجد صور!
Tony, I'm getting hungry.
توني، أنا أشعر بالجوع.
Tony.
توني.
You're a sad sack of shit.
أنت كيس حزين من القذارة.
Hey, sorry, folks. Tony is otherwise engaged.
مرحبًا، آسف يا جماعة. توني مشغول بأمور أخرى.
If you ended up too drunk to find your way home
إذا انتهى بك الأمر في حالة سكر شديدة بحيث لا تتمكن من العثور على طريقك إلى المنزل
and I have to come looking for you again,
ويجب علي أن أعود للبحث عنك مرة أخرى،
I'm going to lose it on you, Tony.
سأخسرها عليك، توني.
It's going to be the last straw, and I mean it!
ستكون هذه هي القشة الأخيرة، وأنا أعني ذلك!
Dipshit.
أحمق.
Hey, I forgot about these.
مهلا، لقد نسيت هذا.
Oh, good. See if they still work.
حسنًا، انظر إن كان لا يزال يعمل.
Hi, Sheila. How're you doin'?
مرحباً شيلا، كيف حالك؟
Testing.
اختبار.
- Oh, really? -  Have you seen him?
- أوه، حقا؟ - هل رأيته؟
- Yeah, he left a while ago. -  Testing, testing.
- نعم، لقد غادر منذ فترة. - اختبار، اختبار.
- Uh huh. -  Let me know.
- أوه هاه. - دعني أعرف.
- Of course. -  Thank you.
- بالطبع. - شكرا لك.
- All right. Take care, honey. -  Bye.
- حسنًا. اعتني بنفسك يا عزيزتي. - مع السلامة.
Finally talked to the power company.
أخيرًا تحدثت مع شركة الطاقة.
They said they're working on it, whatever that means.
قالوا إنهم يعملون على ذلك، مهما كان معنى ذلك.
But the whole city's a mess.
لكن المدينة كلها في حالة من الفوضى.
Power lines are down. It's--it's Armageddon.
خطوط الكهرباء مقطوعة. إنه يوم القيامة.
What's--what's wrong?
ما هو-ما هو الخطأ؟
Uh, I just got off the phone with Sheila,
أوه، لقد انتهيت للتو من التحدث عبر الهاتف مع شيلا،
and she said Tony isn't home yet,
وقالت أن توني لم يصل إلى المنزل بعد،
so she's really worried.
فهي قلقة حقًا.
That's weird. Maybe...
هذا غريب. ربما...
maybe he followed the rainbow
ربما كان يتبع قوس قزح
to a pot of gold. - What is this?
إلى وعاء من الذهب - ما هذا؟
-  Maybe he did. - Maybe he, just like,
- ربما فعل ذلك. - ربما هو، مثل،
stopped at a pub for a pint.
توقفت في حانة لتناول مشروب.
- Maybe. - To make a point.
- ربما. - لإثبات وجهة نظري.
Whoa.
واو.
-  Jesus. -  Huh.
- يسوع. - هاه.
That's wild. -  Wow.
هذا بري. - واو.
Do you hear that?
هل تسمع ذلك؟
There's a lot of them.
هناك الكثير منهم.
Charlie, easy.
تشارلي، سهل.
They're just--they're just talking to each other.
إنهم فقط يتحدثون مع بعضهم البعض.
Having a little coyote convention.
عقد مؤتمر صغير حول الذئب.
Darn.
الرتق.
Enough with the games.
كفى من الألعاب.
Oh, my God.
يا إلهي.
You guys, look.
يا شباب، انظروا.
Oh, he looks lost. He looks--looks scared, huh?
أوه، يبدو تائهًا. يبدو... يبدو خائفًا، أليس كذلك؟
It's sad when they lose their pack.
من المحزن عندما يفقدون قطيعهم.
Have you lost your way home?
هل فقدت طريقك إلى المنزل؟
- Oh, God. -  Jesus.
- يا إلهي. - يسوع.
Uh, Chloe. Why don't you take Charlie inside, honey?
آه، كلوي. لماذا لا تأخذين تشارلي إلى الداخل يا عزيزتي؟
Uh... yeah.
أوه... نعم.
Take Charlie.
خذ تشارلي.
Whoa, easy.
واو، سهل.
-  What about you guys? - We're right behind you.
- ماذا عنكم يا رفاق؟ - نحن خلفكم مباشرة.
- Yeah, yeah. - Go ahead, honey.
- نعم، نعم. - تفضل، عزيزتي.
Get him out of here. - Right behind you.
أخرجوه من هنا. - خلفك مباشرة.
Easy. Nice and easy.
سهل. لطيف وسهل.
Just closing the garage. -  Scott?
فقط إغلاق المرآب. - سكوت
- Yeah? - Hey, Scott.
- نعم؟ - مرحبًا سكوت.
- I'm working on it. - Oh, come on.
- أنا أعمل على ذلك. - أوه، هيا.
- Come on. Gotta go.
- هيا. يجب أن أذهب.
Oh! Oh, shit.
أوه! أوه، اللعنة.
-  Oh. - Oh, my god.
- أوه. - يا إلهي.
Hah.
هاه.
I think it wanted to eat you.
أعتقد أنه أراد أن يأكلك.
No...
لا...
Maybe just a nibble.
ربما مجرد قضمة.
Yeah.
نعم.
Tony!
توني!
Baby!
طفل!
Motherfuckers!
أيها الأوغاد!
Get the hell out of my house!
أخرج من منزلي فورا!
Get away!
ابتعد!
Get away. Get away! Get away!
ابتعد. ابتعد! ابتعد!
Get out.
اخرج.
Fuck.
اللعنة.
This is fun.
هذا ممتع.
It's like we're having a campout inside, in our house.
إنه وكأننا نقيم مخيمًا داخل منزلنا.
Chloe gets a nice slice.
تحصل كلوي على شريحة لطيفة.
Here you go.
ها أنت ذا.
And bon appetit. Mm-mm.
وشهية طيبة .
What is that?
ما هذا؟
It's like, um... it's sort of a meat.
إنه مثل، أمم... إنه نوع من اللحوم.
Yeah. It's good. You'll love it.
نعم، إنه جيد. ستحبه.
Honey. No one wants your fake meats.
عزيزتي، لا أحد يريد لحومك المزيفة.
I'll just have bread and water.
سوف أتناول فقط الخبز والماء.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
You're not a prisoner, Chloe.
أنت لست سجينًا، كلوي.
Are you sure?
هل أنت متأكد؟
Because this feels like torture.
لأن هذا يبدو مثل التعذيب.
I don't know why you won't just let me heat up
لا أعلم لماذا لا تسمح لي بالتسخين
the frozen dinners. - Oh yeah, please.
العشاء المجمد. - أوه نعم، من فضلك.
Heat up the frozen meals with no power.
تسخين الوجبات المجمدة بدون كهرباء.
I'd love to see this.
سأحب أن أرى هذا.
You gonna make a little fire in the kitchen?
هل ستشعل نارًا صغيرة في المطبخ؟
Gas is different than electric.
الغاز يختلف عن الكهرباء.
-  Different bills.
- فواتير مختلفة
-  Yeah. -  That's right.
- نعم. - هذا صحيح.
-  Mm-hm. - You got a smart mom.
- ممم-هم - لديك أم ذكية.
Whoa.
واو.
They are wild.
إنهم متوحشون
They don't want free thinkers.
إنهم لا يريدون مفكرين أحرارًا.
No, no, no.
لا، لا، لا.
They want little robots marching in line
إنهم يريدون روبوتات صغيرة تسير في خط مستقيم
to the sound of whatever story they want you to believe.
على صوت أي قصة يريدونك أن تصدقها.
Goddamn, they said that runs this country.
يا إلهي، لقد قالوا أن هذا هو ما يحكم هذا البلد.
No, I'm not gonna take off my shirt.
لا، لن أخلع قميصي.
Fuck you. Pervert.
إذهب إلى الجحيم. أيها المنحرف.
What was I saying?
ماذا كنت أقول؟
Okay. Yeah, the lizards.
حسنًا. نعم، السحالي.
Um...
واحد...
um... what...
اممم... ماذا...
was that?
كان ذلك؟
What's gotten into them?
ماذا حصل لهم؟
Maybe they are hungry.
ربما أنهم جائعون.
Yeah.
نعم.
They wouldn't turn down food.
لن يرفضوا الطعام.
I'm gonna try it.
سأحاول ذلك.
Why not.
ولم لا.
Mmmm.
ممممم.
No, no. God.
لا، لا. يا إلهي.
It's good.
إنه جيد.
Um... hello?
اممم...مرحبا؟
What the fuck was that?
ماذا كان هذا بحق الجحيم؟
Oh, my God.
يا إلهي.
What?
ماذا؟
Okay, screw this. I'm getting out of here.
حسنًا، لا داعي لهذا. سأخرج من هنا.
Um... hi.
اممم...مرحبا.
Bye-bye.
وداعا وداعا.
Go.
يذهب.
What the fuck.
ماذا بحق الجحيم.
Fuck!
اللعنة!
See you next time around, baby.
نراكم في المرة القادمة يا عزيزي.
Hey.
يا.
Fuck. Fuck!
اللعنة. اللعنة!
You scared the shit out of me.
لقد أرعبتني بشدة.
Uh...
أوه...
Where the fuck have you been?
أين كنت بحق الجحيم؟
Charging my phone in your car.
شحن هاتفي في سيارتك.
I got stuck in a scroll.
لقد علقت في مخطوطة.
I'm not fucking paying you for that.
أنا لا أدفع لك مقابل ذلك.
Actually, I'm glad you're back.
في الواقع، أنا سعيد بعودتك.
Listen, I need a favor.
اسمع، أنا بحاجة إلى معروف.
I need you to help me.
أحتاج إليك لمساعدتي.
I need you to--I need you to help me grieve.
أحتاج إليك لمساعدتي في الحزن.
Um...
واحد...
God, do you hear that?
يا إلهي هل تسمع ذلك؟
I need you to help me hurt.
أحتاج إليك لمساعدتي على الأذى.
Can you help me hurt?
هل يمكنك مساعدتي في الأذى؟
Yeah. I can do that.
نعم، أستطيع فعل ذلك.
Yeah.
نعم.
You've been a bad boy.
لقد كنت فتى سيئا.
Oh, God!
يا إلهي!
You're such a sad, pathetic loser.
أنت خاسر حزين ومثير للشفقة.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
أوه نعم. نعم.
Poor little boy. Daddy doesn't love you.
يا مسكين، أبوك ما بيحبك.
Yeah. Ah!
نعم. اه!
Feel that pain.
أشعر بهذا الألم.
- It hurts so bad. -  Bitch!
- إنه يؤلمني بشدة. - أيها العاهرة!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
نعم، نعم، نعم.
Punish me.
عاقبني.
I want you to punish me.
أريدك أن تعاقبني.
Yeah.
نعم.
Yeah, more. More. -  There you go.
نعم، أكثر. أكثر. - هذا كل ما في الأمر.
There you go.
هناك تذهب.
You're a little snowflake bitch.
أنت فتاة صغيرة مثل ندفة الثلج.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. Tell me-- -  There you go.
- نعم، نعم، نعم. أخبرني-- - ها أنت ذا.
Tell me I'll never have another pet.
أخبرني أنني لن أحصل على حيوان أليف آخر أبدًا.
I'll never have another pet.
لن أحصل على حيوان أليف آخر أبدًا.
Yeah.
نعم.
Oh, don't stop. Oh.
أوه، لا تتوقف. أوه.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God, Trip.
يا إلهي. يا إلهي، تريب.
They got inside.
لقد دخلوا إلى الداخل.
Who got inside?
من دخل إلى الداخل؟
What's wrong? Chill. - They got inside.
ما الخطب؟ اهدأ. - لقد دخلوا.
- I'm not inside. - Sorry.
- أنا لست بالداخل. - آسف.
Fuck off!
إذهب إلى الجحيم!
Get back here, you bitch!
عودي إلى هنا أيتها العاهرة!
Yo! Oh fuck!
يا! يا إلهي!
Bitch!
العاهرة!
Where the fuck are you?!
أين أنت بحق الجحيم؟!
My God!
يا إلاهي!
Ah fuck!
آه اللعنة!
Ah!
اه!
Ah, Trip!
اه، رحلة!
I'm so happy that you made it.
أنا سعيد جدًا لأنك فعلت ذلك.
I'm so sorry that I left.
أنا آسف جدًا لأنني غادرت.
I promise I will never do that again.
أعدك أنني لن أفعل ذلك مرة أخرى.
I promise I will never, ever do that again.
أفعل ذلك مرة أخرى أبدًا.
Fucking promise.
وعد سخيف.
What the fuck am I supposed to do with it?
ماذا علي أن أفعل به؟
One of those fuckers comes in,
يأتي أحد هؤلاء الأوغاد،
you smack the living shit out of it.
أنت تصفعه بقوة.
With this?
مع هذا؟
Give me one of those. - What? Are you fucking nuts?
أعطني واحدة منها. - ماذا؟ هل أنت مجنون؟
You'd shoot me.
سوف تطلق النار علي.
Come on, motherfucker.
هيا أيها الوغد.
Come on, bitch.
تعالي يا عزيزتي
They can open doors?
هل يمكنهم فتح الأبواب؟
Sorry.
آسف.
You bitch!
يا لك من عاهرة!
Ah!
اه!
Zombie. Someone's asleep.
زومبي. أحدهم نائم.
No. The neck.
لا. الرقبة.
Adjusting the neck. Walking.
ضبط الرقبة. المشي.
Walking out.
الخروج.
The spine?
العمود الفقري؟
Chiropractor. -  So stupid.
معالج العمود الفقري. - غبي جدا
-  Lunatic. - Can't give up.
- مجنون. - لا أستطيع الاستسلام.
Neck. Wait, sshhh...
رقبة. انتظر، سششش...
What was that?
ماذا كان هذا؟
Is Trip lighting up fireworks?
هل تريب يشعل الألعاب النارية؟
That checks.
هذا التحقق.
So, Chloe. Chloe.
حسنًا، كلوي. كلوي.
Chloe, Chloe, come on.
كلوي، كلوي، هيا.
Chloe, Chloe.
كلوي، كلوي.
Why is he setting them off inside?
لماذا يطلقهم في الداخل؟
I don't know. He's an idiot.
لا أعلم، إنه أحمق.
I mean-- -  Sshh.
أعني-- - ششش
Yeah, what is that?
نعم ما هذا؟
You don't think he shot that poor girl, do you?
هل تعتقد أنه لم يطلق النار على تلك الفتاة المسكينة؟
I don't think those are fireworks.
لا أعتقد أن هذه ألعاب نارية.
He's probably--
ربما هو--
Charlie!
تشارلي!
Go grab him.
اذهب وأمسكه.
-  Scott, come on. - Okay. I'll go get him.
- سكوت، هيا. - حسنًا. سأذهب لأحضره.
You guys stay here.
أنتم ابقوا هنا.
Ah, it's my turn when I come back.
أه، لقد جاء دوري عندما أعود.
You know, I'm gonna call 911.
هل تعلم أنني سأتصل بالرقم 911؟
I don't-- something feels weird.
لا أشعر بشيء غريب.
Please hold.
يرجى الانتظار.
All operators are currently assisting other callers.
جميع المشغلين يساعدون المتصلين الآخرين حاليًا.
Shit.
اللعنة.
Charlie. Hey.
تشارلي. مرحبا.
Come on, buddy.
تعال يا صديقي.
Ah, there you are.
اه، أنت هناك.
Thanks for interrupting the game, Charlie.
شكرا لك على مقاطعة اللعبة، تشارلي.
Turd.
غائط.
Come on, buddy.
تعال يا صديقي.
Come on, good boy.
هيا أيها الصبي الصالح.
Come on. Easy.
هيا. سهل.
Hey, hey. Take it easy.
مهلا، مهلا. خذ الأمر ببساطة.
Is it really that...
هل هذا حقا...؟
bad in there?
سيء هناك؟
Whoa.
واو.
What is going on tonight?
ماذا يحدث الليلة؟
What the hell?
بحق الجحيم؟
Yeah, Charlie.
نعم تشارلي.
Tough guy. You wouldn't last two minutes out there.
يا رجل قوي. لن تصمد هناك لدقيقتين.
You okay?
هل انت بخير؟
Yeah. I'm good.
نعم، أنا بخير.
It's wild out there.
إنه أمر جامح هناك.
Ow!
أوه!
- Oh, God. - God damn it.
- يا إلهي. - اللعنة عليك.
- Get him, Scott. - Yes, I know.
- امسكه، سكوت. - نعم، أعرف.
I'll get him.
سأحصل عليه.
Liv, get back inside.
ليف، ارجعي إلى الداخل.
Oh, my God.
يا إلهي.
Mom.
أمي
Chloe, go!
كلوي، اذهبي!
- Run! -  Get back inside.
- اركض! - ارجع إلى الداخل.
Oh, my God.
يا إلهي.
What about Dad?
ماذا عن أبي؟
He's a fast runner.
إنه عداء سريع.
I've never seen him run in my life.
لم أرى قط أنه يركض في حياتي.
Charlie. Charlie.
تشارلي. تشارلي.
Ah, shit!
اه، اللعنة!
Fucking Charlie.
تشارلي اللعين.
Mom? Mom?
أمي؟ أمي؟
Yeah.
نعم.
Mom, this is all my fault.
أمي، كل هذا خطئي.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
I saw a coyote and I-- and it looked hungry,
رأيت ذئبًا وبدا جائعًا،
so I fed it.
لذلك أطعمته.
And then the next day, there were two of them,
وفي اليوم التالي، كان هناك اثنان منهم،
so I fed them both.
لذلك أطعمتهم كلاهما.
I thought if stopped feeding them,
اعتقدت أنه إذا توقفت عن إطعامهم،
they would stop coming but they didn't stop.
سيتوقفون عن المجيء ولكنهم لم يتوقفوا.
Mom, they didn't stop.
أمي، لم يتوقفوا.
Honey. Oh, Chloe. Honey.
عزيزتي. أوه، كلوي. عزيزتي.
It's all my fault.
إنه خطئي كله.
No, Chloe. Look at me.
لا يا كلوي، انظري إليّ.
This is not normal behavior.
هذا ليس سلوكا طبيعيا.
Okay.
تمام.
Charlie.
تشارلي.
Hey, Trip. It's Scott.
مرحباً، تريب. أنا سكوت.
Just looking for my dog.
أبحث فقط عن كلبي.
Don't shoot me.
لا تطلق النار علي.
Oh, my God.
يا إلهي.
He's got a jungle in his living room.
لقد حصل على غابة في غرفة معيشته.
It's wild.
إنه بري.
Of course he does.
بالطبع يفعل.
Charlie. Hey.
تشارلي. مرحبا.
Here, here, Charlie.
هنا، هنا، تشارلي.
Come on, Charlie.
هيا يا تشارلي.
Charlie, fuck.
تشارلي، اللعنة.
Uh...
أوه...
Trip, did I hear gunshots in here?
رحلة، هل سمعت طلقات نارية هنا؟
What the fuck.
ماذا بحق الجحيم.
Charlie.
تشارلي.
Help me... Stu.
ساعدني...ستو.
Oh! Whoa! Hey! Don't shoot!
أوه! واو! هي! لا تطلق النار!
Stay the fuck away.
ابقى بعيدا عن هذا المكان.
It's okay. It's okay. It's me.
لا بأس. لا بأس. أنا.
I don't even know who the fuck you are.
أنا لا أعرف حتى من أنت.
Scott. We met.
سكوت. لقد التقينا.
I'm the neighbor.
انا الجار.
You don't want to shoot the neighbor.
لا تريد أن تطلق النار على جارك.
I'm so sorry. I...
انا اسف جدا. انا...
It's okay. It's okay.
لا بأس. لا بأس.
I'm just gonna open the door, okay?
سأفتح الباب فقط، حسنًا؟
Can you put the gun down, please?
هل يمكنك وضع السلاح جانبا من فضلك؟
Yeah. I'm so--I'm so sorry.
نعم. أنا آسف جدًا.
It's okay.
لا بأس
They got in.
لقد دخلوا.
They were everywhere.
لقد كانوا في كل مكان.
There were so many of them. - Okay.
لقد كان هناك الكثير منهم. -حسنا.
I tried to stay and fight with him,
حاولت البقاء والقتال معه،
I did, but he insisted.
لقد فعلت ذلك، لكنه أصر.
He was so brave.
لقد كان شجاعا جدا.
He said, “Julie, go, go. Get out of here.”
قال: "جولي، اذهبي، اذهبي. اخرجي من هنا."
So I did. I...
ففعلت ذلك. أنا...
I ran in here and then I--
لقد ركضت إلى هنا ومن ثم--
oh, God, I could hear him screaming out there.
يا إلهي، لقد سمعت صراخه هناك.
Suddenly he stopped.
توقف فجأة.
It sounded like they were eating him.
لقد بدا الأمر وكأنهم كانوا يأكلونه.
I'm so sorry.
أنا آسف جدًا.
That's awful.
هذا فظيع.
It's not your fault.
إنه ليس خطؤك.
You--you... you did what you could do.
أنت... أنت... لقد فعلت ما بوسعك فعله.
Yeah. I did everything I could.
نعم لقد فعلت كل ما بوسعي.
Listen. I gotta get back to my family.
اسمع، يجب أن أعود إلى عائلتي.
You should come with me.
ينبغي عليك أن تأتي معي.
I think if we go through the backyards, really, really--
أعتقد أنه إذا ذهبنا عبر الساحات الخلفية، حقًا، حقًا--
No. There's no way I'm walking out there.
لا، لا توجد طريقة تمكنني من الخروج هناك.
I can't stay here. I have to go to my--
لا أستطيع البقاء هنا. عليّ الذهاب إلى...
We can drive.
نحن قادرون على القيادة.
Okay, great. Okay, um...
حسنًا، رائع. حسنًا، أم...
would you do me a favor and go first,
هل يمكنك مساعدتي والذهاب أولاً؟
so you block my view,
لذلك أنت تحجب رؤيتي،
because the sight of blood makes me really woozy.
لأن رؤية الدم تجعلني أشعر بالدوار حقًا.
Just the thought of what I saw in there
مجرد التفكير فيما رأيته هناك
is--is--is making me kind of lightheaded.
إنه يجعلني أشعر بالدوار نوعًا ما.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Never knew coyotes to behave like this.
لم أكن أعلم أن الذئاب تتصرف بهذه الطريقة.
Once in a while you hear about them eating a little dog,
من حين لآخر تسمع عن أكلهم لكلب صغير،
but this is fucking nuts.
لكن هذا مجنون تماما.
Don't worry about it.
لا تقلق بشأن هذا
Shit. It's me.
يا للعار، أنا.
I'm sorry. Sorry.
انا اسف. انا اسف.
Oh! Oh, it's Devon.
أوه! أوه، إنه ديفون.
- Who? - He's our pest guy.
- من؟ - إنه الرجل المزعج لدينا.
Our pest control guy.
رجل مكافحة الآفات لدينا.
Devon. Devon, thank God.
ديفون. ديفون، الحمد لله.
Uh-huh, you called?
أوه، هل اتصلت؟
I did?
فعلتُ؟
Shit, I did.
يا للعار، لقد فعلت ذلك.
Fourteen times. I'm sorry, but listen, listen.
أربع عشرة مرة. أنا آسف، لكن اسمع، اسمع.
We could really use your help right now.
نحن بحاجة ماسة لمساعدتكم الآن.
You need to give the poison time to work.
يجب عليك إعطاء السم وقتًا حتى يعمل.
Not gonna happen overnight.
لن يحدث هذا بين عشية وضحاها.
Three to 10 days to fully get rid of your problem.
ثلاثة إلى عشرة أيام للتخلص من مشكلتك بشكل كامل.
It's not the rats.
إنها ليست الفئران.
We have a crazy situation here.
لدينا حالة مجنونة هنا.
I'm having a real situation here too,
أنا أواجه موقفًا حقيقيًا هنا أيضًا،
with someone calling me on my night off.
مع شخص يتصل بي في ليلتي الإجازة.
No, no, no, no. It's coyotes.
لا، لا، لا، لا. إنه ذئب البراري.
I will be there before sunrise to check the rat traps.
سأكون هناك قبل شروق الشمس للتحقق من مصائد الفئران.
Devon.
ديفون
Night-night.
ليلة سعيدة.
Shit.
اللعنة.
That sounded like it went well.
يبدو أن الأمر سار على ما يرام.
We gotta get out of here.
علينا أن نخرج من هنا.
Okay.
تمام.
What?
ماذا؟
As soon as we get out there,
بمجرد خروجنا إلى هناك،
you better move your goddamn ass.
من الأفضل أن تحرك مؤخرتك اللعينة.
It's a good thing I'm a fast runner.
من الجيد أنني عداء سريع.
What? I am.
ماذا؟ انا.
That's not good.
هذا ليس جيدا.
Oh, shit. Jesus!
يا إلهي. يا يسوع!
Fucking bitch!
أيتها العاهرة اللعينة!
Fuck!
اللعنة!
-  You... -  Julie.
-أنت... - جولي.
You killed my client before he Venmoed me.
لقد قتلت موكلي قبل أن يرسل لي رسالة على فينمو.
And he was a regular.
وكان منتظما.
Okay. That's--that's good.
حسنًا. هذا جيد.
That's good.
هذا جيد.
You got him.
لقد حصلت عليه.
I think he's dead.
أعتقد أنه ميت.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Please, please, let's go.
من فضلك، من فضلك، دعنا نذهب.
It's not your fault, honey.
إنه ليس خطؤك يا عزيزتي.
No, it's not.
لا، ليس كذلك.
It's all gonna be okay.
كل شيء سيكون على ما يرام.
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
Charlie. It's Charlie, Mom.
تشارلي. أنا تشارلي، يا أمي.
Yes.
نعم.
Charlie.
تشارلي.
Get him, baby. Get him.
إمسكه يا حبيبي.إمسكه.
Oh, God! Come on!
يا إلهي! هيا!
Honey.
عسل.
What is that?
ما هذا؟
It's gonna get inside.
إنه سوف يدخل إلى الداخل.
We're gonna be okay.
سوف نكون بخير.
What is making them so crazy?
ما الذي يجعلهم مجانين إلى هذا الحد؟
Holy shit.
يا إلهي.
- Oh, fuck. - It's the chemtrails.
- أوه، اللعنة. - إنها الكيمتريلز.
The what?
ماذا؟
You know those long strings of white puffy clouds
هل تعرف تلك السلاسل الطويلة من السحب البيضاء المنتفخة؟
behind airplanes? - Yeah, yeah.
خلف الطائرات؟ - نعم نعم.
Okay. Those are chemicals that the government
حسنًا. هذه مواد كيميائية تستخدمها الحكومة
is dumping into the atmosphere to mind control us,
يتم إلقاءه في الغلاف الجوي للسيطرة على عقولنا،
but it's killing all the bees
لكنها تقتل كل النحل
and it's driving all the animals crazy.
وهذا يقود جميع الحيوانات إلى الجنون.
You know, it's like in that movie,
كما تعلم، الأمر يشبه ذلك الفيلم،
you know, the one where all the birds attack everyone.
هل تعلم، تلك اللحظة التي تهاجم فيها جميع الطيور الجميع.
What's it called? Um...
ماذا يسمى؟ امم...
The one with all the birds.
الذي يحتوي على كل الطيور.
The Birds?
الطيور؟
No, that's not the one.
لا، ليس هذا هو الشخص.
It reminds me of this moment.
يذكرني بهذه اللحظة.
But you know, where the birds are coming out her head?
ولكن هل تعلم من أين تخرج الطيور من رأسها؟
And it's really, it's an iconic movie.
وهو في الحقيقة فيلم مميز.
Why don't you know the name of it?
لماذا لا تعرف إسمه؟
I'm pretty sure it's The Birds.
أنا متأكد تمامًا من أنها الطيور.
No, .
لا، .
Oh, man, it's gonna come to me later.
أوه، يا رجل، سوف يأتي إليّ لاحقًا.
Yeah, agree to disagree.
نعم، نتفق على الاختلاف.
Let's--could you give me the keys?
دعنا... هل بإمكانك أن تعطيني المفاتيح؟
Oh, fuck!
أوه، اللعنة!
What?
ماذا؟
Oh, God. The fucking--
يا إلهي. اللعين--
The gate isn't gonna open because the power is out.
لن يتم فتح البوابة بسبب انقطاع الكهرباء.
Oh, shit.
يا للقرف.
Oh, God. My bad.
يا إلهي، خطئي.
Ever been off roading?
هل سبق لك القيادة على الطرق الوعرة؟
No.
لا.
Hold on.
انتظر
Slow down. Oh, no.
أبطئ. أوه، لا.
You couldn't have just parked it?
لم يكن بإمكانك ركنها فقط؟
Sorry.
آسف.
We needed the force
كنا بحاجة إلى القوة
- Oh, my God. - to go through the gate.
- يا إلهي - للمرور عبر البوابة.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
- Barely. -  Sorry.
- بالكاد. - آسف.
Told you I'd never gone off roading.
أخبرتكِ أنني لم أذهب أبدًا إلى الطرق الوعرة.
Don't sue me. Remember, I--
لا تقاضني. تذكر، أنا...
remember I saved you.
تذكر أنني أنقذتك.
Oh, shit. I gotta go see a chiropractor.
يا إلهي، يجب أن أذهب لرؤية طبيب العظام.
Oh, fuck. - Oh, my God.
أوه، اللعنة. - يا إلهي.
Get the fuck off my husband!
إبتعد عن زوجي!
Hey, babe.
مرحبا يا حبيبتي.
Let's go inside.
دعنا نذهب إلى الداخل.
Liv, is that you?
ليف، هل هذه أنت؟
You look like a superhero.
أنت تبدو وكأنك بطل خارق.
Chloe, close the door. Close the door.
كلوي، أغلقي الباب. أغلقي الباب.
Quick, Chloe.
سريعًا، كلوي.
You got it. Oh, good.
لقد حصلت عليه. أوه، جيد.
Hey. Hey, guys.
أهلاً، أهلاً يا شباب.
What have you two been up to?
ماذا كنتما تفعلان؟
Uh, yeah. Just--just hanging out.
نعم، فقط ... فقط نقضي وقتًا ممتعًا.
Liv.
حياة.
Julie.
جولي.
Bet you didn't think your weekend
أراهن أنك لم تعتقد أن عطلة نهاية الأسبوع الخاصة بك
would turn out like this.
سوف تصبح مثل هذا.
Honestly, in my line of work, you never know.
بصراحة، في مجال عملي، لا أحد يعرف ما قد يحدث.
Oh.
أوه.
Oh, is that Charlie?
أوه، هل هذا تشارلي؟
Is he okay?
هل هو بخير؟
He's good.
إنه جيد.
-  Yeah. - Yeah, he's good.
- نعم. - نعم، إنه جيد.
It's good to see you.
يسعدني رؤيتك.
-  Oh, there's, uh--oh. - Right.
- أوه، هناك، أوه-أوه. - صحيح.
Hooooo.
هووو.
Okay. Let me help you.
حسنًا، دعني أساعدك.
Oof. Is it bad?
اووف. هل هو سيء؟
Is it bad?
هل هو سيء؟
Uh, don't look.
أوه، لا تنظر.
-  Why? -  Sorry. Not that bad.
- لماذا؟ - آسف. ليس سيئًا.
- Why don't you want me to look? - No, it's okay.
- لماذا لا تريدني أن أنظر؟ - لا، لا بأس.
Let's just--let's get you upstairs.
دعنا فقط - دعنا نأخذك إلى الطابق العلوي.
- Oh, I saw it. - Come on.
- أوه، لقد رأيته. - هيا.
Okay. Come on.
حسناً، هيا.
Remember your breathing exercises.
تذكر تمارين التنفس الخاصة بك.
Whoo. Okay.
ووه. حسنًا.
Oh. You're bleeding all over the carpet.
أوه، دمك ينزف على السجادة.
Oh, don't--don't.
أوه، لا--لا تفعل.
So, uh, your dad...
إذن، والدك...
what's his deal?
ما هي الصفقة الخاصة به؟
He's got a thing about blood.
لقد حصل على شيء عن الدم.
Yeah.
نعم.
On Thanksgiving, he, uh,
في عيد الشكر، هو، اه،
he cut his finger carving our turkey
لقد قطع إصبعه أثناء تقطيع الديك الرومي الخاص بنا
and passed out right in the mashed potatoes.
وأغمي عليه مباشرة في البطاطس المهروسة.
Julie chuckles]
جولي تضحك]
Okay. Okay.
حسنًا. حسنًا.
You're definitely gonna need stitches,
من المؤكد أنك ستحتاج إلى غرز،
and probably a rabies shot.
وربما حقنة ضد داء الكلب.
That's great.
هذا عظيم.
Something to look forward to when I get out of here.
شيء أتطلع إليه عندما أخرج من هنا.
Yeah.
نعم.
You know, Chloe thinks this is all her fault.
هل تعلم أن كلوي تعتقد أن هذا كله خطأها.
What? Why?
ماذا؟ لماذا؟
She's been feeding the coyotes.
لقد كانت تطعم الذئاب.
She said they looked hungry.
قالت أنهم يبدو جائعين.
She's... she's being sweet, really.
إنها... إنها لطيفة حقًا.
No. This is-- I don't know what this is.
لا. هذا-- لا أعرف ما هذا.
This is almost like some kind of mass hysteria.
يبدو هذا الأمر وكأنه نوع من الهستيريا الجماعية.
It's like when those monkeys started attacking the tourists
إنه مثل عندما بدأت تلك القردة بمهاجمة السياح
in Thailand.
في تايلاند.
Yeah, when whales ram boats.
نعم، عندما تصطدم الحيتان بالقوارب.
Right.
يمين.
Why wouldn't Chloe tell me about the coyotes?
لماذا لم تخبرني كلوي عن الذئاب؟
Because you're not here.
لأنك لست هنا.
What are you talking about?
ماذا تتحدث عنه؟
You're not here.
أنت لست هنا.
You're not with us.
أنت لست معنا.
You're not with your daughter.
أنت لست مع ابنتك.
You're always working. You know?
أنت تعمل دائمًا. هل تعلم؟
I mean, it's like if we come
أعني، الأمر كما لو أننا أتينا
and try and have a conversation with you in your office,
وحاول إجراء محادثة معك في مكتبك،
it's like walking on eggshells.
إنه مثل المشي على قشر البيض.
- We don't know what to say. - I'm working.
- لا نعرف ماذا نقول. - أنا أعمل.
I--I--I finally got this great--
أنا-أنا-أخيرًا حصلت على هذا الشيء العظيم-
Yeah, we're aware you're working.
نعم، نحن ندرك أنك تعمل.
We are very well aware
نحن ندرك جيدًا
Everything I do is for you and Chloe.
كل ما أفعله هو من أجلك ومن أجل كلوي.
For this house, for this life.
من أجل هذا البيت، من أجل هذه الحياة.
Would you rather be in that shitty one bedroom
هل تفضل أن تكون في تلك الغرفة المفردة البائسة؟
in Koreatown?
في كورياتاون؟
Above the noisy restaurant?
فوق المطعم الصاخب؟
Could never sleep?
لم أستطع النوم أبدًا؟
Fucking toilet always backing?
هل المرحاض اللعين يتراجع دائمًا؟
Yes. Yes.
نعم نعم.
I loved that place because we were with you.
لقد أحببت هذا المكان لأننا كنا معك.
We were with you.
لقد كنا معك.
We miss you.
إننا نفتقدك.
Scott? - What?
سكوت؟ - ماذا؟
When you left Trip's, was it on fire?
عندما غادرت تريب، هل كان مشتعلا بالنيران؟
Huh?
هاه؟
It's important to not panic.
من المهم عدم الذعر.
We just have to figure out a way off this hill,
علينا فقط أن نجد طريقة للخروج من هذا التل،
and we're going to get off this hill.
وسوف ننزل من هذا التل.
Okay? I know it looks bad outside,
حسناً؟ أعلم أن الوضع يبدو سيئاً في الخارج،
but there are roads that are open,
ولكن هناك طرق مفتوحة،
and we just have to contact somebody.
وعلينا فقط أن نتواصل مع شخص ما.
So any working cell phones, iPads, anything?
فهل هناك أي هواتف محمولة أو أجهزة iPad أو أي شيء يعمل؟
No. Everything's dead.
لا، كل شيء ميت.
Chloe. You have no juice?
كلوي. ليس لديك عصير؟
No.
لا.
You really have no juice?
هل حقا ليس لديك عصير؟
Yeah. I mean, I used it.
نعم، أعني أنني استخدمته.
Okay, that's okay. That's okay.
حسنًا، لا بأس. لا بأس.
Um... -  Sorry.
اممم... - آسف.
Excuse me? I'm so--
عذرا؟ أنا كذلك--
...and we are...
...و نحن...
What?
ماذا؟
You had a phone this whole time that works?
هل كان لديك هاتف يعمل طوال هذا الوقت؟
Yeah. I was charging it in Trip's car
نعم. كنت أشحنه في سيارة تريب.
when those wolves started coming around.
عندما بدأت تلك الذئاب في القدوم.
First of all, they're coyotes.
أولاً وقبل كل شيء، هم الذئاب.
Secondly-- - Okay, whatever.
ثانياً-- - حسنًا، لا بأس.
I doubt Trip cared if they were coyotes or cows
أشك في أن تريب كان يهتم إذا كانوا ذئابًا أم أبقارًا
when they were eating his lungs.
عندما كانوا يأكلون رئتيه.
They ate his lungs?
لقد أكلوا رئتيه؟
No, no, no, honey.
لا، لا، لا، عزيزتي.
They ate some of his lungs, but he was dead.
لقد أكلوا بعضًا من رئتيه، لكنه كان ميتًا.
All right? He died peacefully. - That didn't happen.
حسناً؟ لقد مات بسلام. - لم يحدث ذلك.
I heard him screaming.
سمعته يصرخ
He died very peacefully.
لقد مات بسلام.
Doesn't matter. Can I borrow it, please?
لا يهم. هل يمكنني استعارته من فضلك؟
For what?
لماذا؟
For an emergency call
للمكالمة الطارئة
because of the emergency we're all experiencing.
بسبب حالة الطوارئ التي نمر بها جميعًا.
Okay, sure.
حسنا، بالتأكيد.
Oh, God bless you.
أوه، الله يباركك.
You're at 86%?
هل أنت عند 86%؟
What?!
ماذا؟!
Yeah. Excuse me for being responsible.
نعم. عذراً على تحمل المسؤولية.
I'm stunned.
أنا مذهول.
Please hold--
يرجى الانتظار--
Oh shit. Okay.
يا إلهي. حسنًا.
I'm--I'm--I'm on hold.
أنا-أنا-أنا في الانتظار.
Can you do me a huge favor and just stay on the phone?
هل يمكنك أن تفعل لي خدمة كبيرة وتبقى على الهاتف فقط؟
We're on hold. - Mm-hm.
نحن في الانتظار. - مم-هم.
Remember the emergency. Take a look outside.
تذكّر حالة الطوارئ. انظر إلى الخارج.
Okay? - Yeah.
حسناً؟ - نعم.
All right.
حسنًا.
More ideas, and there are no bad ideas.
مزيد من الأفكار، ولا توجد أفكار سيئة.
Just throw them out. Just--
فقط ارميهم خارجًا. فقط--
What if we build a cage?
ماذا لو بنينا قفصًا؟
Oh. I know I said there are no bad ideas,
أوه، أعلم أنني قلت أنه لا توجد أفكار سيئة،
and I love that you're using your brain.
وأنا أحب أنك تستخدم عقلك.
But how would we ever build one big enough
ولكن كيف يمكننا بناء واحد كبير بما فيه الكفاية؟
to fit all the coyotes inside and to get them to go in it?
لإدخال جميع الذئاب إلى الداخل وإجبارهم على الدخول إليه؟
Keep it going. Okay, I don't mean to be negative--
استمر. حسنًا، لا أقصد أن أكون سلبيًا...
But it wouldn't be for them.
ولكن هذا لن يكون بالنسبة لهم.
It'd be for us, like, like a shark cage.
سيكون الأمر بالنسبة لنا، مثل قفص القرش.
Yeah.
نعم.
That could work.
قد ينجح هذا.
No way.
مستحيل.
I--I could build it.
أنا أستطيع بناءه.
I could. - No, honey. You know what?
أستطيع. - لا يا عزيزتي. هل تعلمين؟
It doesn't come with instructions,
لا يأتي مع التعليمات،
and you're not very good with your hands.
وأنت لست جيدًا جدًا في استخدام يديك.
I know you want to be that person.
أعلم أنك تريد أن تكون هذا الشخص.
I see it in your-- - I am that person.
أرى ذلك فيك --- أنا هذا الشخص.
Hey, hey, hey. Where are we?
هيه، هيه، هيه. أين نحن؟
What's the address? - Oh, okay, okay.
ما هو العنوان؟ - أوه، حسنًا، حسنًا.
Six-two--
ستة اثنان--
The call just dropped.
لقد انقطعت المكالمة للتو.
Fuck.
اللعنة.
I forgot to close the window.
نسيت إغلاق النافذة.
Hide.
يخفي.
Where is Chloe?
أين كلوي؟
Under the stairs.
تحت الدرج.
Oh, fuck.
اوه، اللعنة.
Chloe.
كلوي.
Go.
يذهب.
Chloe, run!
كلوي، اركضي!
Stay.
يقضي.
Heel.
الجميع.
Sit. Sit.
اجلس. اجلس.
Liv! Liv! - No, Scott!
حياة! حياة! - لا، سكوت!
No.
لا.
Scott! Help!
سكوت! النجدة!
Shit! Shit!
اللعنة! اللعنة!
Scott!
سكوت!
Did I get it?
هل حصلت عليه؟
Yeah.
نعم.
Go!
يذهب!
Chloe! Hang on, kid.
كلوي! انتظري يا صغيرتي.
Chloe, Chloe. I'm coming, kid.
كلوي، كلوي. أنا قادم يا صغيرتي.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God, Chloe!
يا إلهي. يا إلهي، كلوي!
Scott, help me get her out. -  Um...
سكوت، ساعدني على إخراجها. - أم...
Okay. It's okay.
حسناً، لا بأس.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
يا إلهي. يا إلهي.
It's okay. It's okay, baby.
لا بأس. لا بأس يا حبيبتي.
You're okay. You're okay.
أنت بخير. أنت بخير.
Chloe, look at me.
كلوي، انظري إليّ
Is Charlie okay?
هل تشارلي بخير؟
He's in the laundry. Look in the laundry.
هو في الغسيل. انظروا في الغسيل.
Char--Charlie. Look for Charlie in the laundry hamper.
شارلي. ابحث عن تشارلي في سلة الغسيل.
Okay. Oh, there he is.
حسنًا. أوه، ها هو.
He's okay. He's okay.
إنه بخير.إنه بخير.
It's okay. You did so good.
لا بأس، لقد فعلتِ جيدًا.
I'm scared.
أنا خائفة.
- It's okay if you're scared.
- لا بأس إذا كنت خائفة.
You're okay.
أنت بخير
There's a first aid kit in the bathroom.
هناك مجموعة الإسعافات الأولية في الحمام.
Go!
يذهب!
Okay.
تمام.
Okay. Okay. You're okay.
حسناً. حسناً. أنت بخير.
Okay. You're okay.
حسناً، أنت بخير.
You're gonna be okay.
سوف تكون بخير.
No, no, no, Scott! Don't you dare.
لا، لا، لا يا سكوت! لا تجرؤ.
Oh, God. It's okay. I'm here. I'm here. It's okay.
يا إلهي، لا بأس. أنا هنا. أنا هنا. لا بأس.
Honey.
عسل.
Sweetie. Chloe.
عزيزتي. كلوي.
Thank God.
الحمد لله.
Yeah. She's doing good.
نعم، إنها بخير.
I'm so sorry.
أنا آسف جدا.
What are you talking about?
ماذا تتحدث عنه؟
I shouldn't have fed them.
لا ينبغي لي أن أطعمهم.
No, no.
لا لا.
Kiddo, you didn't do this.
يا صغيري، أنت لم تفعل هذا.
You didn't do this.
لم تفعل هذا.
Mom says I'm gonna have a scar like a vampire bite.
أمي تقول أنني سأحصل على ندبة مثل لدغة مصاص الدماء.
Oh, that'll be-- that'll be cool.
أوه، هذا سيكون-- هذا سيكون رائعا.
Yeah, that's right.
نعم، هذا صحيح.
Vampires like a-- what did we say--
مصاصو الدماء يحبون-- ماذا قلنا--
a mythical lady of the night?
سيدة الليل الأسطورية؟
That's a euphemism for a prostitute
هذا تعبير ملطف عن عاهرة
dating back to the 17th century.
يعود تاريخها إلى القرن السابع عشر.
Oh. I didn't even know you were here.
أوه. لم أكن أعلم أنك هنا.
Hey, thank you, Julie.
مرحبًا، شكرًا لك، جولي.
You're welcome.
على الرحب والسعة.
Honey, I'm gonna talk to your dad a minute.
عزيزتي، سأتحدث مع والدك لمدة دقيقة.
Why don't you rest? Okay?
لماذا لا ترتاح؟ حسنًا؟
Okay.
تمام.
No one is coming for us.
لا أحد يأتي إلينا.
We have to get her to the ER.
علينا أن ننقلها إلى غرفة الطوارئ.
Hey. Build it.
مهلا، قم ببنائه.
Okay, I can do this.
حسنًا، يمكنني القيام بذلك.
I can do this.
انا قادر على فعل هذا.
Let's see here. Some music.
دعونا نرى هنا. بعض الموسيقى.
80s badgers.
الغرير في الثمانينيات.
80s badgers? 80s bangers.
أغاني الغرير في الثمانينيات؟ أغاني الثمانينيات الرائعة.
That's perfect.
هذا ممتاز.
What--what is all that noise?
ماذا...ما كل هذا الضجيج؟
Your dad's building something.
والدك يبني شيئًا ما.
Is that safe?
هل هذا آمن؟
Fuck.
اللعنة.
90s jams.
مربى التسعينيات.
That'll do.
هذا سوف يفعل.
This is kind of wrong.
هذا خطأ نوعا ما.
Okay... okay.
حسنًا... حسنًا.
Liv.
حياة.
Liv, you hear me up there?
ليف، هل تسمعيني هناك؟
Yeah, I hear you.
نعم، أسمعك.
I just wanna say... you were right.
أريد فقط أن أقول... أنك كنت على حق.
I've treated you guys like background art
لقد عاملتكم مثل فن الخلفية
of some stupid comic--
من بعض القصص المصورة الغبية--
And I'm so sorry.
وأنا آسف جداً.
And Chloe,
وكلوي،
I don't even remember when she stopped calling me Dad.
لا أتذكر حتى متى توقفت عن مناداتي بأبي.
Started calling me Scott.
بدأ يناديني سكوت.
I just kind of ignored it.
لقد تجاهلت الأمر نوعًا ما.
And I see the way you look at me and I...
وأنا أرى الطريقة التي تنظر بها إلي وأنا...
and I know you're just bracing for disappointment.
وأنا أعلم أنك تستعد للإحباط.
And I'm so sorry.
وأنا آسف جداً.
Liv?
حياة؟
Sorry, Scott. I...I didn't catch that.
آسف، سكوت. أنا... لم أفهم ذلك.
Can you say that again?
هل يمكنك أن تقول ذلك مرة أخرى؟
Really?
حقًا؟
Yeah, it was just .
نعم لقد كان فقط .
Uh...
أوه...
No, I just--I was— when did it cut out?
لا، أنا فقط - أنا كنت - متى انقطع؟
I heard “I want to,” and then nothing.
سمعت "أريد ذلك"، ثم لم أسمع شيئًا.
Oh .
أوه .
I was just saying I want to... go on a trip
كنت أقول فقط أنني أريد... الذهاب في رحلة
when all this is over.
عندما ينتهي كل هذا
That'd be really nice.
سيكون ذلك لطيفًا حقًا.
We haven't done that in a long time.
لم نفعل ذلك منذ وقت طويل
Yeah, I'd really like that.
نعم، أود ذلك حقًا.
That'd be fun.
سيكون ذلك ممتعا.
Okay.
تمام.
Okay, I'll see-- I'll see you soon.
حسنًا، سأرى-- سأراك قريبًا.
Someone's coming.
شخص ما قادم
Oh, someone's coming.
أوه، شخص ما قادم.
He doesn't know.
إنه لا يعلم.
We have to warn him.
علينا أن نحذره.
No, no, no. Don't!
لا، لا، لا تفعل!
He's a professional.
إنه محترف.
He'll be fine.
سيكون بخير.
Welcome to Hollywood.
مرحباً بكم في هوليوود.
Ah, Jesus.
اه ، يسوع.
Storms shut down the hills,
العواصف أغلقت التلال،
but I snaked through the back roads like a rat.
لكنني تسللت عبر الطرق الخلفية مثل الفأر.
End of days.
نهاية الأيام.
Look at what we got here.
انظر إلى ما حصلنا عليه هنا.
You boys thirsty?
هل أنتم عطشى؟
No, get away. It's not safe.
لا، ابتعد. المكان ليس آمنًا.
They're gonna fucking kill you.
إنهم سوف يقتلونك
Get back in the van!
ارجع إلى الشاحنة!
Don't be a hero.
لا تكن بطلا
What's going on up there?
ماذا يحدث هناك؟
The pest control guy is here.
رجل مكافحة الآفات موجود هنا.
- What? He is? -  Yes.
- ماذا؟ هو؟ - نعم.
Should I--should I keep going?
هل ينبغي لي أن أستمر؟
You want to dance, you four legged freak?!
هل تريد أن ترقص، أيها الكائن ذو الأرجل الأربعة؟!
Come at me. Hey.
تعال إلي. مهلا.
What are you doing?!
ماذا تفعل؟!
You're gonna miss the K-9 barbecue!
سوف تفتقد حفل شواء K-9!
Oh, my--!
أوه، يا إلهي--!
Oh, my God!
يا إلهي!
Oh, no. I can't see this.
أوه لا، لا أستطيع رؤية هذا.
Oh, don't. Yeah, you don't want to see this.
أوه، لا تفعل. نعم، لا تريد رؤية هذا.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Think they got him.
أعتقد أنهم حصلوا عليه
Look, I don't know how your little invention
انظر، أنا لا أعرف كيف اختراعك ​​الصغير
is coming along, but you might want to hurry
إنه قادم، ولكن قد ترغب في الإسراع
or it's gonna be fucking useless.
أو سيكون الأمر عديم الفائدة تمامًا.
Well, you can't rush a masterpiece.
حسنًا، لا يمكنك التسرع في إنجاز تحفة فنية.
Yes, you can!
نعم يمكنك ذلك!
Is Charlie with you guys?
هل تشارلي معكم يا رفاق؟
Yeah, he's here with Chloe.
نعم، إنه هنا مع كلوي
Okay.
تمام.
What?
ماذا؟
Is this a bad idea?
هل هذه فكرة سيئة؟
This is definitely a bad idea.
هذه بالتأكيد فكرة سيئة.
This is great.
هذا عظيم.
This is a great idea.
هذه فكرة رائعة.
Oh, my God.
يا إلهي.
What are you--oh.
ماذا أنت-أوه.
Did you get trapped in here by that mean pest control guy?
هل وقعت في الفخ هنا بسبب ذلك الرجل المتخصص في مكافحة الآفات؟
Come here. Oh, my God.
تعال هنا. يا إلهي.
Were you the one making all that noise?
هل كنت أنت من صنع كل هذا الضجيج؟
That's okay.
لا بأس. لا بأس.
We shouldn't be hanging out in here.
لا ينبغي لنا أن نبقى هنا.
Gotta get you out of here.
يجب أن أخرجك من هنا.
There's a fire coming.
هناك حريق قادم.
We're gonna--we're gonna come back for you.
سوف نعود إليك.
Okay? All right.
حسناً؟ حسناً.
Come on, buddy.
تعال يا صديقي.
I got you.
حصلت عليك.
God, I hope you like Charlie.
اللهم إني أتمنى أن يعجبك تشارلي.
They just wanted their puppies.
لقد أرادوا كلابهم فقط.
That's why they were so pissed.
لهذا السبب كانوا غاضبين جدًا.
What? Is the cage built?
ماذا؟ هل تم بناء القفص؟
Pretty much, but um, I gotta do this on my own.
تقريباً، لكن، عليّ أن أفعل هذا بنفسي.
Dad, this was a really bad idea,
أبي، كانت هذه فكرة سيئة حقًا
and sharks break into cages sometimes.
وأسماك القرش تقتحم الأقفاص في بعض الأحيان.
Don't do this. - It's gonna be fine.
لا تفعل هذا - سيكون كل شيء على ما يرام.
Chloe, this was your idea, and it's gonna work.
كلوي، هذه كانت فكرتك، وسوف تنجح.
It's gonna work.
إنه سوف يعمل.
Okay, nice and easy.
حسنًا، لطيف وسهل.
Oh, it works.
أوه، إنه يعمل.
There he is.
ها هو ذا.
Do you see?
هل ترى؟
I see something.
أرى شيئا.
Hey, I've got something you want.
مهلا، لدي شيء تريده.
You want to make a trade?
هل تريد إجراء تجارة؟
You wanna make a trade?
هل تريد إجراء صفقة؟
He didn't have instructions.
لم يكن لديه تعليمات.
I got something you want.
لدي شيء تريده.
He did good.
لقد فعل الخير.
Ah! Pig!
اه! خنزير!
Shit! Stop! You turn your--
يا إلهي! توقف! أدر...
My God! I can't watch this.
يا إلهي! لا أستطيع مشاهدة هذا.
Please stop. Stop it!
من فضلك توقف. توقف!
Oh, fuck.
اوه، اللعنة.
Oh, me neither.
أوه، أنا أيضا.
What does that mean?
ماذا يعني ذلك؟
I wish you guys could translate what just happened.
أتمنى أن يتمكن بعضكم من ترجمة ما حدث للتو.
Oh, my God.
يا إلهي.
Mm-mm.
ممممم.
Guys, I'm gonna make the hand off.
يا شباب، سأقوم بإزالة اليد.
Chloe, this is gonna work.
كلوي، هذا سوف ينجح.
Dad, don't do this.
أبي لا تفعل هذا.
Just have faith in your old man.
فقط كن على ثقة بوالدك.
Okay.
تمام.
I hope those aren't my last words.
أتمنى أن لا تكون هذه كلماتي الأخيرة.
Come on.
تعال.
Come on, Dad.
تعال يا أبي.
Here we go, guys.
هنا نذهب يا شباب.
You ready to go home?
هل أنت مستعد للذهاب إلى المنزل؟
I know I am.
انا أعلم أنني كذلك.
Oops, sorry. All right.
عفواً، تمام .
Nice and easy.
لطيف وسهل
Go ahead.
استمر.
Okay. Nice and easy. Nice and easy.
حسناً. لطيف وسهل. لطيف وسهل.
Want to make a trade.
أريد أن أقوم بالتجارة.
Okay. Okay... Easy.
حسنًا. حسنًا... سهل.
Just... easy.
فقط... سهل.
Easy. Relax.
سهل. استرخي.
Okay. All right.
حسناً. حسناً.
They were under my house. I didn't put them there.
لقد كانوا تحت منزلي. لم أضعهم هناك.
Nice and easy.
لطيف وسهل
And we're all gonna live happily ever after.
وسوف نعيش جميعا في سعادة دائمة.
I know you just want to keep your family safe.
أعلم أنك تريد فقط الحفاظ على سلامة عائلتك.
Me too.
أنا أيضاً.
Your family for mine. Okay?
عائلتك من عائلتي. حسنًا؟
You're gonna go home.
سوف تذهب إلى المنزل.
Go back to your family.
عودي إلى عائلتك.
I'm gonna go back to mine.
سأعود إلى بلدي.
Come on.
تعال.
You got this.
لقد حصلت على هذا.
Come on, Dad.
تعال يا أبي.
Come on.
تعال.
Here you go, bud.
تفضل يا صديقي.
Here you go.
ها أنت ذا.
Good? Good.
جيد؟ جيد.
Okay. Okay, buddy.
حسنًا. حسنًا يا صديقي.
You're gonna go home.
سوف تذهب إلى المنزل.
Chloe, it worked.
كلوي، لقد نجح الأمر.
Oh, my God!
يا إلهي!
Honey, he did it.
عزيزتي، لقد فعلها.
You can come out now.
يمكنك الخروج الآن.
We're gonna get out of this hill.
سوف نخرج من هذا التل.
Oh, honey.
أوه، عزيزتي
All right, let's get the fuck out of here.
حسنًا، دعنا نخرج من هنا.
Oh.
أوه.
fuck me!
ألعنني!
Get off me!
إبتعد عني!
We had a deal!
لقد كان لدينا صفقة!
You okay?
هل انت بخير؟
I thought you had a thing with blood?
اعتقدت أن لديك شيئًا مع الدم؟
Oh yeah.
أوه نعم.
I think I'm getting over it.
أعتقد أنني تجاوزت الأمر.
Come on. - Come on.
تعال. - تعال.
Okay.
تمام.
Everybody in? Everything okay?
هل الجميع هنا؟ كل شيء على ما يرام؟
Just drive the van!
فقط قم بقيادة الشاحنة!
Okay. God!
حسناً. يا إلهي!
♪ Hallelujah, hallelujah ♪
♪ هللويا، هللويا ♪
♪ Halle-llelujah, hallelujah
♪ هللويا، هللويا
- We're going too slow, Scott. - I--I--look.
- نحن نسير ببطء شديد، سكوت. - أنا-أنا-أنظر.
- Daddy, faster! - Are you for real?
- بابا أسرع! - هل أنت حقيقي؟
My--my foo--It is. It is. It's not mine.
يا إلهي، إنه ليس ملكي.
♪ Hallelujah, halle-llelujah
♪ هللويا، هللويا
Pretty cool bite you have.
لديك لدغة جميلة جدًا.
Drive the van, honey.
قم بقيادة السيارة يا عزيزتي.
That's the fastest it goes. It's a stick.
هذه هي أسرع طريقة. إنها عصا.
I haven't driven a stick in a while.
لم أقود سيارة ذات ناقل حركة يدوي منذ فترة.
Stick a couple of ladies of the night back here.
ألصق زوجًا من سيدات الليل هنا مرة أخرى.
I don't think that's appropriate.
لا أعتقد أن هذا مناسب.
Oh, my God.
يا إلهي.
Is that our house?
هل هذا بيتنا؟
Not anymore.
ليس بعد الآن.
I don't care.
لا أهتم.
I got everything I need in this van.
لقد حصلت على كل ما أحتاجه في هذه الشاحنة.
Yeah.
نعم.
Except for my comic book collection.
باستثناء مجموعتي من القصص المصورة .
Hey, where are you going?
مهلا، إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
The original Fantastic Four.
الأربعة المذهلون الأصليون.
Who cares?
من يهتم؟
Mm-hm.
مم-هم.
Ah. And first appearance Thor.
اه. والظهور الأول لثور.
Every--everything's in the van.
كل شيء موجود في الشاحنة.
But yeah, we're alive.
ولكن نعم، نحن على قيد الحياة.
Mm-hm. Yeah.
مممم. نعم.
I'll get them at some trade show.
سأحصل عليهم في بعض المعارض التجارية.
Not so fast.
ليس بهذه السرعة.
But maybe because I have them in a lock box,
ولكن ربما لأنني أحتفظ بها في صندوق مغلق،
so maybe they're protected.
لذا ربما يكونون محميين.
Just drive the van, Scott,
فقط قم بقيادة الشاحنة، سكوت،
and as far away from Hollywood as possible.
وبعيدًا عن هوليوود قدر الإمكان.
Come on. Give me all you got.
تعال. أعطني كل ما لديك.
Come on!
تعال!
Yeah!
نعم!
♪ I'm dying in LA
♪ أنا أموت في لوس أنجلوس
♪ Visit stands pretty
♪ الزيارة تقف جميلة
♪ Wanna be your big name
♪ أريد أن أكون اسمك الكبير
♪ Just like Marilyn
♪ تمامًا مثل مارلين
♪ I'm dying in LA
♪ أنا أموت في لوس أنجلوس